[
  {
    "category": "Quotes and Memes",
    "question": "After stating \"I don't like Nintendo anymore, it's for babies\", what version of Call of Duty does Arin proclaim that he wants to play?",
    "answers": [
      "COD: Pew Pew",
      "COD: Shoot a Man",
      "COD: Missed",
      "COD: Plus Ultra"
    ],
    "correct": 2,
    "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f_fDKl0dHmA",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "Quotes and Memes",
    "question": "According to Arin, what is the name of a disease you get from chewing too much?",
    "answers": ["Twilt", "Spoodles", "Sprankton", "Tamould"],
    "correct": 3,
    "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xrbdfeva2bM",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "Quotes and Memes",
    "question": "According to a Grumps bit, Ashman's life cleaned up after meeting which invented mega-man character?",
    "answers": ["Splashman", "Trashman", "Stashman", "Mashman"],
    "correct": 2,
    "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uUILjiniT88",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "Quotes and Memes",
    "question": "When Arin and Dan were young children, Dan shit himself 17 times at a Dairy Queen in Kansas.",
    "answers": [true, false],
    "correct": 2,
    "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gpgn3rmu0aM",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What is former Game Grumps member Jontron's real name?",
    "answers": [
      "Jonathan Malkovich",
      "Jon Irwin",
      "Jonathan Birdman",
      "Jonathan Jafari"
    ],
    "correct": 4,
    "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/JonTron",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "How did Arin and Jon meet?",
    "answers": ["YouTube", "Newgrounds", "High School", "Twitter"],
    "correct": 1,
    "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/JonTron#Sargon_of_Akkad_livestream_controversy",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Uploaded on July 18, 2018, the first video ever uploaded to their channel was of the hosts doing what?",
    "answers": [
      "Playing Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate",
      "Playing Kirby Super Star",
      "Singing \"SMASH!\" by Starbomb",
      "Playing The Legend of Zelda"
    ],
    "correct": 2,
    "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_Grumps",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Which of these common Game Grumps guests originally inspired the name \"Game Grumps\" when he told Jon and Arin about their tendency to be \"grumpy\"?",
    "answers": ["Matt Watson", "Suzy Berhow", "Ross O'Donovan", "Brian Wecht"],
    "correct": 3,
    "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_Grumps",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What was the original platform for the show?",
    "answers": ["Blog", "YouTube", "Podcast", "Netflix"],
    "correct": 3,
    "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_Grumps",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  },
  {
    "category": "Quotes and Memes",
    "question": "What name does Dan's father accidentally say when trying to refer to the music service \"Spotify\"?",
    "answers": ["The Googles", "Spoofy", "The AOL", "Spootifee"],
    "correct": 2,
    "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LuPi2YN5vGg",
    "answeredCorrectly": ""
  }
]
